{ "categories":
       [ { "name": "River Questions",
           "answers":
            [ { "question": "Do you have livestock/s?", "answer": 0 },
              { "question": "If yes, what kind of livestock/s?",
                "answer": [ 1, 3 ] },
              { "question": "How do you manage livestock manure?",
                "answer": [ 1, 3 ] },
              { "question": "How do you deal with your waste disposal?",
                "answer": [ 1, 2 ] },
              { "question": "Have you done the following activities in the river?",
                "answer": [ 0, 1 ] },
              { "question": "Do you have a pet?", "answer": 0 },
              { "question": "Where does your pet litter?", "answer": [ 1 ] },
              { "question": "Do you have toilet facility?", "answer": 1 },
              { "question": "If yes, what type of toilet facility it is?",
                "answer": null },
              { "question": "If no, where do you urinate/defecate?",
                "answer": [ 1, 2 ] } ] },
         { "name": "Standards of living and water sources",
           "answers":
            [ { "question": "What is your housing status of ownership?",
                "answer": 2 },
              { "question": "What are your sources of potable water?",
                "answer": [ 0, 3 ] },
              { "question": "What are the sources of your secondary sources?",
                "answer": [ 1, 3 ] } ] },
         { "name": "Health, Sanitation and Hygiene",
           "answers":
            [ { "question": "Check the symptoms that members of your family are displaying",
                "answer": [ 0, 1 ] },
              { "question": "Are there any members of the family diagnosed with waterborne diseases such as:",
                "answer": [ 1, 3 ] },
              { "question": "Which of the following practices prevent waterborne related diseases?",
                "answer": [ 1 ] } ] },
         { "name": "Ecological Sanitation",
           "answers":
            [ { "question": "Do you have a garden or agricultural land?",
                "answer": 1 },
              { "question": "If yes, do you use a fertilizer?", "answer": null },
              { "question": "What kind of fertlizer do you use?", "answer": null } ] } ] }